Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; XIII.
  - Events, 7.
    - International Events
      - Briggs, Everett, U.S. Ambassador to Portugal, Washington, DC, March 30, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 24)
      - Brittan, Sir Leon, Vice President of the European Communities Commission, Washington, DC, January 14, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 25)
      - Burke, Ray, Justice Minister of Ireland, TREVI related, Washington, DC, January 23, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 26)
      - Burney, Derek, Canadian Ambassador and Edouard Brunner, Swiss Ambassador regarding Canadian/Swiss Asset Forfeiture, Washington, DC, September 21, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 27)
      - Busby, Morris, U.S. Ambassador-at-Large for Counter Terrorism, Washington, DC, November 14, 1990, July 18, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 28)
      - Campbell, Kim, Canadian Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, April 18, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 29)
      - Canadian Embassy Dinner, Washington, DC, October 30, 1988 (Box 808, Folder 30)
      - Carpizo, Dr. Jorge, Mexican Commission on Human Rights, Washington, DC, April 15, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 31)
      - Catto, Henry, Director, USIA, former U.S. Ambassador to the United Kingdom (U.K.), Washington, DC, March 19, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 32)
      - Chemical Action Task Force, Washington, DC, October 30, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 33)
      - Cheng, Cai, Chinese Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, October 4-15, 1988 (Box 808, Folder 34)
      - Chulabhorn, Princess of Thailand, Washington, DC, April 2, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 35)
      - CIA Chinese Briefing, Cai Cheng, Chinese Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, October 4, 1988-October 15, 1988 (Box 808, Folder 36)
      - Colombian Drug Summit (Cartagena), Washington, DC, February 12, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 37)
      - Conseil D'Etat, letter regarding Attorney General's trip to Paris, France, June 7, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 38)
      - Corcuera, Jose Luis, Spanish Interior Minister, Washington, DC, March 2, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 39)
      - Cordoba, Dr. Jose, Advisor Mexico President Carlos Salinas, Washington, DC, November 14, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 40)
      - Cossiga, Francesco, President of Italy, Washington, DC, October 11, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 41)
      - Counter Terrorism Briefing, FBI, Washington, DC, February 9, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 42)
      - Craxi, Bettino, Prime Minister of Italy, Washington, DC, October 20, 1988 (Box 808, Folder 43)
      - Cruz, Rogelio, Attorney General of Panama, Washington, DC, July 25, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 44)
      - Davidson, Lynne, U.S. Department of State Speech Writer, Washington, DC, September 25, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 45)
      - Delius, Carlos, Bolivia Ambassador to the U.S., Washington, DC, May 17, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 46)
      - Deutsche Oper Berlin Performance at the Kennedy Center, Germany Ambassador Jurgen Ruhfus, Washington, DC, June 11, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 47)
      - Digital Telephony, Meeting with Bill Barr, Washington, DC, June 20, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 48)
      - Diplomatic Corps Dinner, Washington, DC, February 1, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 49)
      - Dubinin, Vladimiovich Yuri, Soviet Union Ambassador to the U.S., Washington, DC, May 18, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 50)
      - Eagleburger, Lawrence, U.S. Deputy Secretary of State, Washington, DC, October 5, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 51)
      - Einaudi, Luigi, U.S. Ambassador to the OAS (Organization of American States), Washington, DC, April 16, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 52)
      - Endara, Guillermo, President of Panama, Washington, DC, April 27, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 53)
      - Evans, Gareth, Australia Minister of Foreign Affairs and Trade, Washington, DC, October 8, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 54)
      - Federov, Nikolay, Minister of Justice, Republic of Russia, Washington, DC, March 8, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 55)
      - Ford, Guillermo, Vice President of Panama, Washington, DC, March 29, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 56)
      - Ford, Jaime, Panama Ambassador to the U.S., Washington, DC, July 1, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 57)
      - Foreign Travel Program Briefing, Washington, DC, February 15, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 58)
      - Franco-American Judicial Exchange Luncheon, Washington, DC, September 7, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 59)
      - Fraser, Lord Advocate of Scotland, Washington, DC, January 24, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 60)
      - Freivalds, Laila, Sweden Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, April 2, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 61)
      - Gava, Antonio, Italian Minister of the Interior, Washington, DC, April 4, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 62)
      - Gaviria, Cesar, President of Colombia, Washington, DC, September 28, 1990, February 26, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 63)
      - Gelb, Bruce, U.S. Ambassador to Belgium, Washington, DC, June 21, 1991 (Box 808, Folder 64)
      - Gelbhard, Richard, U.S. Ambassador to Bolivia, Washington, DC, February 28, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 65)
      - Gennaro, di Giuseppe, United Nations Fund for Drug Abuse Council (UNFDAC), Washington, DC, August 24, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 66)
      - Gillespie, Charles A., Jr., U.S. Ambassador to Chile, Washington, DC, February 10, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 67)
      - Godhino, Minister Jose Silveira, Minister of Internal Administration to Portugal, Washington, DC, August 22, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 68)
      - Gorbachev State Dinner, Washington, DC, May 31, 1990 (Box 808, Folder 69)
      - de Greiff, Monica, Minister of Justice to Colombia, Washington, DC, August 24, 1989 (Box 808, Folder 70)
      - Haleem, Mohammed, Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of Pakistan, Washington, DC, June 8, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 1)
      - Han, Xu, Ambassador of China, Washington, DC, May 3, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 2)
      - Han, Xu, Ambassador of China, Farewell Luncheon, Washington, DC, August 11, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 3)
      - Havel, Vaclav, President of Czechoslovakia, Washington, DC, February 20, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 4)
      - Hecht, Chic, U.S. Ambassador to the Bahamas, Washington, DC, May 30, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 5)
      - Hocke, Jean Pierre, United Nations Commissioner for Refugees, Washington, DC, June 6, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 6)
      - Hogg, Douglas Honorable, British Under Secretary for Home Affairs, Washington, DC, May 25, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 7)
      - Horyn, Mykhailo, Popular Movement of Ukraine, Washington, DC, September 11, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 8)
      - Huffington, Roy, U.S. Ambassador to Austria, Washington, DC, April 16, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 9)
      - Hurd, Douglas, British Foreign Secretary, Washington, DC, January 29, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 10)
      - Hurtado Cabrera, Carlos, Minister of Government of Nicaragua, Washington, DC, May 15, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 11)
      - Hyun, Hong-Choo, Korea Ambassador to the U.S., Washington, DC, June 24, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 12)
      - International Club #1, Washington, DC, September 26, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 13)
      - Italian American Working Group, April 4, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 14)
      - Iturralde, Carlos, Foreign Minister of Bolivia and Carlos Saaverda, Bolivia Minister of Interior, Migration, and Justice, Washington, DC, July 22, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 15)
      - Jacoby, Ambassador of Switzerland, Washington, DC, November 16, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 16)
      - Jamaica Mutual Legal Assistance Treaty (MLAT) signing, Jamaica, July 3, 1989-July 4, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 17)
      - Johansson, Bengt, Sweden Minister for Public Administration, Washington, DC, January 7, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 18)
      - Keeley, Robert, U.S. Ambassador to Greece; L. Paul Bremer, U.S. Ambassador at Large for Counter terrorism, Washington, DC, November 21, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 19)
      - Kolleck, Teddy, Mayor of Jerusalem, Washington, DC, November 16, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 20)
      - Kulcsar, Dr. Kalman, Minister of Justice of Hungary, Washington, DC, March 30, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 21)
      - Lacalle, Luis, President of Uruguay, Washington, DC, February 5, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 22)
      - LaFontant, Jewel, U.S. Ambassador at Large and U.S. Coordinator for Refugee Affairs, Washington, DC, September 11, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 23)
      - Lane, Bill, U.S. Ambassador to Australia, Washington, DC, February 24, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 24)
      - Levitsky, Melvin, Assistant Secretary for the Bureau of International Narcotics Matters, the Department of State, Washington, DC, May 30, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 25)
      - Lewis, Doug, Attorney General of Canada, Washington, DC, January 25, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 26)
      - Lintner, Eduard, Parliamentary State Secretary, German Interior Ministry, Washington, DC, April 11, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 27)
      - Loeschnak, Frank, Austrian Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, November 29, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 28)
      - Loudjev, Dimitar, Deputy Prime Minister of Bulgaria, Washington, DC, July 23, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 29)
      - Lushchikov, Sergey, Minister of Justice of the USSR (Union of Soviet Socialist Republics), Washington, DC, February 19, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 30)
      - Mackay, Lord Chancellor and Ambassador Antony Acland of Great Britain, Washington, DC, February 14, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 31)
      - MacLean, Roberto, Peru Ambassador to the U.S., Washington, DC, June 28, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 32)
      - Majewski, Henryk, Interior Minister of Poland, Washington, DC, March 22, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 33)
      - Major, John, British Foreign Secretary, Washington, DC, September 11, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 34)
      - MALI--Dinner, Washington, DC, October 6, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 35)
      - Marchenko, Dr. Mikhail, Dean, Moscow State University Law School, Washington, DC, February 14, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 36)
      - Marker, Jamshed, Pakistan Ambassador to the U.S., undated (Box 809, Folder 37)
      - Matlock, Jack, U.S. Ambassador to the Soviet Union, Washington, DC, November 22, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 38)
      - Mayhew, Patrick, Attorney General of the United Kingdom, Washington, DC, June 26, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 39)
      - Medina, Gustavo, Attorney General of Ecuador, Washington, DC, June 20, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 40)
      - Melady, Thomas, U.S. Ambassador to the Holy See, Washington, DC, May 29, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 41)
      - Meridor, Dan, Justice Minister of Israel, Washington, DC, June 16, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 42)
      - Mexico, Background information regarding drug trafficking events, November 1988 (Box 809, Folder 43)
      - Mexico, U.S./Mexico Attorneys General Border Conference, Santa Fe, NM, May 3, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 44)
      - Miller, William Green, American Committee on U.S.-Soviet Relations, Washington, DC, September 21, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 45)
      - de Mita, Ciriaco, Prime Minister of Italy, Washington, DC, December 15, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 46)
      - Monge Aguero, Jorge, Costa Rican Minister of National Planning and Economic Policy, Washington, DC, April 4, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 47)
      - Moore, Jonathan, U.S. Ambassador, Refugee Affairs Coordinator, Washington, DC, January 12, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 48)
      - Moore, Richard, U.S. Ambassador to Ireland, Washington, DC, July 28, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 49)
      - Mugica, Enrique, Spanish Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, October 15, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 50)
      - Murata, Ambassador and Mrs. Ryohei of Japan, Concert/Dinner, Washington, DC, April 2, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 51)
      - Murata, Ryohei, Ambassador of Japan, Washington, DC, April 12, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 52)
      - Murray, John, Attorney General of Ireland; MacKernan, Padraic, Ambassador of Ireland to the U.S., Washington, DC, February 6, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 53)
      - McDonald, Margret, Ambassador of the Bahamas to the U.S., Washington, DC, October 21, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 54)
      - McNamara, Ted, U.S. Ambassador to Colombia, Minister of Justice of Colombia Guillermo Alcid, Plazas Meeting, Washington, DC, September 17, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 55)
      - McWeeney, Sean, Attorney General of the Bahamas, Washington, DC, February 9, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 56)
      - NSC (National Security Council) Briefings, Washington, DC, October 5, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 57)
      - Ndinga-Oba, Antoine, Minister of Foreign Affairs and Martin Adouki, Ambassador of Congo to the United Nations (UN), Washington, DC, October 10, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 58)
      - Negroponte, John, U.S. Ambassador to Mexico, Washington, DC, August 7, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 59)
      - Ney, Edward, U.S. Ambassador to Canadian, Washington, DC, June 14, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 60)
      - Orlov, Vladimir, Soviet Union Central Election Committee, Washington, DC, November 8, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 61)
      - Ortega, Temistocles, Colombia Vice Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, March 17, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 62)
      - Pan Am 103, Washington, DC, September 21, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 63)
      - Park, Tong-Jin, Ambassador of the Republic of Korea, Washington, DC, August 21, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 64)
      - Petrignani, Rinaldo, Italian Ambassador to the U.S., Washington, DC, August 3, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 65)
      - Philippines, Background information regarding Philippines drug trafficking, undated (Box 809, Folder 66)
      - Pilliod, Charles, U.S. Ambassador to Mexico, Washington, DC, January 2, 1989 (Box 809, Folder 67)
      - Porte, Luis, Deputy Attorney General of Mexico, Washington, DC, August 25, 1988 (Box 809, Folder 68)
      - Quayle, Marilyn, Trip to the USSR, Washington, DC, November 8, 1990 (Box 809, Folder 69)
      - Queen Elizabeth, State Visit, Washington, DC, May 15, 1991 (Box 809, Folder 70)
      - Raiz, Karmella, Soviet Refusenik, Washington, DC, January 18, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 1)
      - Rattray, Rafael "Carl," Minister of Justice and Attorney General of Jamaica, Washington, DC, May 19, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 2)
      - Ray, Robert, Australian Defense Minister, Washington, DC, October 8, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 3)
      - Richter, Leon, Czechoslovakian Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, June 21, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 4)
      - Roger, Oscar, Attorney General of Argentina, Washington, DC, May 1, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 5)
      - Rosch, Thomas, Chairman of American Bar Association (ABA) Antitrust Section, Washington, DC, September 19, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 6)
      - Roskens, Ronald, Agency for International Development, Washington, DC, March 15, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 7)
      - Rowny, Ambassador Edward, Special Advisor to the President and Secretary of State for Arms Control Matters, Washington, DC, January 9, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 8)
      - Rubinstein, Elyakim, Israel Cabinet Secretary, Washington, DC, February 24, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 9)
      - Ruhfus, Karin, Ambassador of the Federal Republic of Germany, Washington, DC, June 11, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 10)
      - Salinas, Carlos, President of Mexico, Washington, DC, October 3, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 11)
      - Sanguinetti, Julio Maria, President of Uruguay, Washington, DC, September 18, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 12)
      - Sassou, Nguesso, Denis, President of the Congo, Washington, DC, February 14, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 13)
      - Schifter, Dick, U.S. Assistant Secretary of State for Human Rights, Washington, DC, November 30, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 14)
      - Schnaeuble, Wolfgang, West Germany Minister of the Interior, Washington, DC, February 21, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 15)
      - Secchia, Pete, U.S. Ambassador to Italy, Washington, DC, August 23, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 16)
      - Seitz, Raymond, U.S. Ambassador to the United Kingdom (U.K.), Washington, DC, April 30, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 17)
      - Shamir, Yitzhak, Prime Minister of Israel, Washington, DC, April 6, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 18)
      - Shamir, Yitzhak, Quayle Luncheon, Washington, DC, December 12, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 19)
      - Shimojo, Shin'ichiro, Minister of Health and Welfare of Japan, Washington, DC, June 25, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 20)
      - Sofaer, Abraham, Counsel, U.S. Department of State, Washington, DC, September 13, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 21)
      - Sola, Dr. Juan, University of Buenos Aires, Argentina, Washington, DC, October 12, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 22)
      - Solana, Fernando, Mexican Secretary of Foreign Relations, Washington, DC, March 21, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 23)
      - Soviet Officials Meeting, Washington, DC, September 21, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 24)
      - Spanish Riding School, Washington, DC, September 30, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 25)
      - Supreme Soviet Delegation, Washington, DC, November 27, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 26)
      - Queen Sylvia of Sweden, Washington, DC, April 12, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 27)
      - Tate, Senator Michael, Australian Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, June 23, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 28)
      - Taylor, William, Vice President of the International Security Programs, CSIS, Washington, DC, August 10, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 29)
      - Thatcher, Margaret, Dinner hosted by Ambassador Antony Acland, Washington, DC, March 8, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 30)
      - Topornin, Boris, Soviet Institute of State and Law, Washington, DC, March 6, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 31)
      - Trail, George, U.S. Ambassador to Kenya, Washington, DC, June 8, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 32)
      - United Nations Convention Against Illicit Traffic in Drugs, Vienna, Austria, December 20, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 33)
      - United Nations Concert and Dinner, Washington, DC, October 27, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 34)
      - United Nations Vienna Convention Signing and Speech, New York, NY, November 12, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 35)
      - United States/Mexico Binational Commission Meeting, Washington, DC, August 8, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 36)
      - Vallarino, Eduardo, Ambassador of Panama, Washington, DC, June 19, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 37)
      - Vargas, General, Colombian National Police, Washington, DC, September 19. 1990 (Box 810, Folder 38)
      - Vassalli, Giuliano, Italian Minister of Justice, Washington, DC, September 15, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 39)
      - Waddington, David, Embassy Dinner, Washington, DC, February 12, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 40)
      - Waddington, David, British Home Secretary, Washington, DC, February 12, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 41)
      - Walesa, President and Mrs. Lech, Poland, Washington, DC, March 21, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 42)
      - Watchmeister, Wilhelm, Ambassador from Sweden, Washington, DC, January 24, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 43)
      - Wathelet, Melchoir, Belgian Vice Prime Minister, Washington, DC, February 20, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 44)
      - Webster, William, Director of the CIA, Washington, DC, March 5, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 45)
      - Wilkey, Malcolm, American Ambassador to Uruguay, Washington, DC, March 16, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 46)
      - Wilkey, Malcolm, American Ambassador to Uruguay, Office of the Attorney General (OAG) Reception, Washington, DC, May 17, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 47)
      - Wilkins, Howard, U.S. Ambassador to the Netherlands, Washington, DC, December 11, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 48)
      - Williams, Richard, U.S. Ambassador to Mongolia, undated (Box 810, Folder 49)
      - Woo, Roh Tae, President of the Republic of Korea, Luncheon in honor of Vice President Quayle, Washington, DC, July 3, 1991 (Box 810, Folder 50)
      - Wrobleski, Ann, Assistant Secretary of State for International Narcotics Matters, Washington, DC, October 19, 1988 (Box 810, Folder 51)
      - Yakovlev, Veniamin, Justice Minister of the USSR, Washington, DC, August 11-17, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 52)
      - Zappala, Joseph, U.S. Ambassador to Spain, Washington, DC, April 18, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 53)
      - Zaslavski, Ilya, Soviet People's Congress, Washington, DC, September 6, 1989 (Box 810, Folder 54)
      - Zhelev, Zhelyu, President of Bulgaria, Washington, DC, September 26, 1990 (Box 810, Folder 55)
    - Congressional Events
      - Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), Testimony, Washington, DC, October 11, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 55)
      - Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), Briefing for Testimony, Washington, DC, June 21, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 2)
      - Armstrong, William L., Senator, Washington, DC, October 4, 1988 (Box 811, Folder 3)
      - Asian-American Student Quotas, with Gingrich, Hunter, Rohrabacher, and Saiki, Washington, DC, July 18, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 4)
      - Barnard, Congressman Doug, Washington, DC, August 1, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 5)
      - Bartlett, Congressman Steve, Washington, DC, December 17, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 6)
      - Biden, Senator Joseph R., Jr., Washington, DC, January 25, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 7)
      - Biden, Senator and Senators \Metzenbaum and Kennedy, Washington, DC, November 16, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 8)
      - Brooks, Congressman Jack, Washington, DC, March 1, 1989, December 18, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 9)
      - Brooks, Congressman Jack, Lunch, Washington, DC, January 29, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 10)
      - Byrd, Senator Robert, FBI Relocation, Washington, DC, February 22, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 11)
      - Chafee, Senator John and Congressman Ron Machtley, Washington, DC, July 11, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 12)
      - Chemical Diversion and Trafficking Act of 1988, undated (Box 811, Folder 13)
      - Civil Rights Act of 1990, Washington, DC, July 17, 1990, July 19, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 14)
      - Civil Rights Act of 1991, Washington, DC, May 30, 1991, June 3, 1991, June 5, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 15)
      - Civil Rights Act of 1991, House Briefing, Washington, DC, February 6, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 16)
      - Civil Rights Act of 1991, Senate Briefing, Washington, DC, February 6, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 17)
      - Clinger, Congressman and Mrs., Alexandria, VA, November 26, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 18)
      - Congressional Barbecue, Washington, DC, August 1, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 19)
      - Congressional Black Caucus, Washington, DC, January 31, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 20)
      - Congressional Black Caucus, Meeting with President Bush, Washington, DC, June 25, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 21)
      - Congressional Picnic at the White House, Washington, DC, September 15, 1988 (Box 811, Folder 22)
      - Congressional Press Conference on Pornography, Washington, DC, January 27, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 23)
      - Conte, Congressman Silvio, Memorial Service, Washington, DC, February 27, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 24)
      - Conte, Congressman Silvio and Hal Rogers, Justice Appropriations, Washington, DC, September 18, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 25)
      - Conyers, Congressman John (LAPD), Washington, DC, March 14, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 26)
      - Coughlin, Congressman John, TEAM FAD (Fight Against Drugs) Kick-off of the Heroes Challenge Relay Run, Washington, DC, July 25, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 27)
      - Courter, Jim, Washington, DC, September 13, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 28)
      - Crime Bill (1991), Meeting with Congressmen Bob Michel and Representative Members of the House Judiciary Committee, Washington, DC, April 4, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 29)
      - Danforth, Senator John, Washington, DC, June 25, 1991 (Box 811, Folder 30)
      - DeConcini, Senator Dennis, Washington, DC, October 25, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 31)
      - Disabilities Legislation Meeting, Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), Washington, DC, June 20, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 32)
      - Dole Dinner in honor of President and Mrs. Bush and Republican Members of the U.S. Senate, Washington, DC, November 13, 1990 (Box 811, Folder 33)
      - Domenici, Senator Pete, Washington, DC, September 8, 1988 (Box 811, Folder 34)
      - Dornan, Congressman Robert, Washington, DC, May 23, 1989, May 24, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 35)
      - Drug Bill Signing Ceremony, Washington, DC, November 18, 1988 (Box 811, Folder 36)
      - Durenberger, Senator David, Senator Rudy Boschwitz and Congressman Bill Frenzel, Washington, DC, November 17, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 37)
      - Edwards, Congressman Dan and Congressmen Robert Kastenmeier and Romano Mazzoli, Washington, DC, October 12, 1989 (Box 811, Folder 38)